export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following options is not a code editor?",
    choices: ["Visual Studio Code", "Sublime Text", "Atom", "Adobe Photoshop"],
    answer: "Adobe Photoshop",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most widely used programming language?",
    choices: ["JavaScript", "Python", "Java", "C++"],
    answer: "JavaScript",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most widely used operating system on smartphones?",
    choices: ["Android", "iOS", "Windows Phone", "BlackBerry"],
    answer: "Android",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the hypertext transfer protocol used for the World Wide Web?",
    choices: ["HTTP", "FTP", "SMTP", "SSH"],
    answer: "HTTP",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following programming languages is object-oriented?",
    choices: ["Java", "HTML", "CSS", "SQL"],
    answer: "Java",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the main element for structuring the content of a web page?",
    choices: ["HTML", "CSS", "JavaScript", "PHP"],
    answer: "HTML",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following databases is a relational database management system?",
    choices: ["MySQL", "MongoDB", "Redis", "Elasticsearch"],
    answer: "MySQL",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What method is used to add elements to the end of an array in JavaScript?",
    choices: ["push()", "pop()", "shift()", "unshift()"],
    answer: "push()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following options is a JavaScript web development framework?",
    choices: ["React", "Angular", "Vue", "All of the above"],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the result of 2 + '2' in JavaScript?",
    choices: ["4", "22", "NaN", "Error"],
    answer: "22",
  },
];
